<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Services on York TechSoc</title><link>/services/</link><description>Recent content in Services on York TechSoc</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sound</title><link>/services/sound/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/services/sound/</guid><description>We have multiple sound desks available for use including our SQ5 which has 48 Input channels and is able to cope with our largest productions. In addition to this we have several sets of microphones including SM58 and SM57 as well as condenser microphones and a set of drum mics. While we don’t own any, we also frequently work with radio mics and would be able to hire these in for you.</description></item><item><title>Lighting</title><link>/services/lighting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate><guid>/services/lighting/</guid><description>We have a large stock of lighting fixtures, including conventionals, LEDs and Moving fixtures. We also have waterproof uplighters which are perfect for outdoor events. The variety of lights we can provide allow us to support both productions and corporate events. We train our members in how to operate our lights as well as how to best create effective and interesting lighting designs. If you have an initial vision for your production or specific requests for the lighting designer please pass these onto your project manager!</description></item><item><title>Video</title><link>/services/video/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>/services/video/</guid><description>While we do not record events on our own we do own a few pieces of equipment in order that we can operate signage and pre-recorded video at events. If this is something you’re interested in please discuss this with your project manager. If you’re looking for your production or event to be recorded then we frequently work with YSTV in order to do this.</description></item></channel></rss>